

Aldrich Louie L. Aydalla

SEO Team Leader | Digital Marketing Assistant | Technician | Outreach Assistant | Backlink Builder Specialist

Mobile: 09560746873

Email: aldrich.aydalla@gmail.com

Address: #22 Rizal St. Bo. Barretto,

Olongapo City, Zambales

PROFILE

I am an SEO Team Leader of Link Builders with nine years of experience, Digital Marketing Assistant, Outreach Assistant, Data Entry Specialist and a Backlink Building Specialist. With more than a year of managerial background in my field that further develops my interpersonal and leadership skills. Able to lead the completion of simultaneous projects with proper task distribution and time management.

My experiences have allowed me to develop strong time management and organizational skills, which I see as being very important when seeking to work in casual employment.

Full time home-based and online employee.

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Hardware Technician

Kolehiyo Ng Subic

S.Y. 2011 - 2013

On-the-Job Training

Barretto National High School

Assigned as a Computer Laboratory Coordinator; Responsible for monitoring the area, inventory, technical (technician), and supervising all TLE students who utilize the school's computers.

SEMINAR ATTENDED

Winning Work Habits

May 2015

PLDT Innolab, 721 Boni Ave, Mandaluyong, Metro Manila

EXPERTISE

- Proficient in MS Office
- Link Building
- Backlink Building
- Basic SEO Audit
- Google My Business
- Local Listing
- Keywords Research
- Wordpress
- Snapps
- √ Wix
- Drupal 8
- Outreach
- Off-page SEO
- On-page SEO
- Software Tester
- Data Entry
- Troubleshooting
- Knowledge in Photoshop
- Guest Posting
- Article Submission
- Search Engine Submission
- Web Building

Other skills:

- Computer Literate
- Willing to work flexible hours
- Verbal Communication Skills
- Ability to Work Under Pressure
- Decision Making
- Time Management
- Adaptability
- Leadership
- Teamwork
- Creativity

EXPERIENCE

Link Building Specialist

Easy Mode Media

February 2023 - December 2024

- Outreach for potential Guest Posting
- Create Backlink using Copy-cat Method and Do Follow Only
- Publish live articles
- Keyword Research

SEO Link Builder

Rosy Holdings

January 2023 - May 2023

- Outreach for potential Guest Posting
- Create Backlink using Copy-cat Method, Do Follow Only
- Publish live articles

SEO Link Builder

Lead 4 Business

February 2021 - December 2022

- Outreach for potential Guest Posting
- Create Backlink using Copy-cat Method, Relevant (No Follow) and TF Do Follow
- ✓ Web Building 2.0
- Keyword Research

SEO Link Builder

Dotsense Media

September 2021 - December 2022

- Produce x amount of links per week
- Look for a high TF backlinks (Do Follow only)
- Do some SEO VA's task
- Fill all the money site and PNB's sheet and report
- Geo Tagging
- Site Mapping

SEO Team Leader

The SpeedUp Co.

June 2020 – September 2021

- Daily creating backlinks using comments into different blogging or forum website to promote our gaming site and page
- Outreach for potential Guest Posting
- Manually check my members daily output to maintain the quality
- Weekly Huddle for strategy
- End of the month report for each website analyzation
- Searching for Expired Domains for PBN

Backlink Builder Specialist

PC.Game

January 2019 – August 2022

- Daily creating backlinks using comments into different blogging or forum website to promote our gaming site and page
 - o specific metrics trust flow
 - o high quality backlink website
 - o no-follow and do-follow links

Digital Marketing Assistant

Shoutpoll / Interactive Base Inc.

November 2018 - January 2019

- I create keywords
- set-up and put the proper backlinks
- On-page link building
- Promoting a product
- Buy domain
- Layout the website using Drupal and create all the pages
- Social Media Management

Digital Marketing Assistant

Brand Equation

May 2018 – July 2018

- GMB (Google My Business) set-up and posting
- Schedule article or blog posting of different client website
- Local citation every month
- Top listing and NAP consistencies
- Social media marketing and omni-channel digital ad campaigns.

SEO Link Building and Outreach Assistant

Liquid Sport Media

May 2018 – October 2022

- Email potential websites who'd be interested in hosting paid articles for SEO purposes
- Using SEO tools such as Ahrefs
- Using SEO tools such as Majestic
- Bid for price
- Submit article for publishing

SEO Team Leader

Logicgateone Corporation

May 2013 – February 2018

- Individual task distributor
- Monitors the output evaluation
- Daily quality evaluation of individual members
- Entitled to create a Summary Report at the end of the day to keep track of daily performance.